Speaker 1: In offices, There are certain rooms that you can access and that you can't access based on your role. So if we think about a building, you could create a framework that says these rooms are accessible by these people. And in each room, there are rules for how we function. There is a conference room. There is a lunchroom. There is a phone booth room, And each of all of those rooms have different purposes. And here, there is a framework for how they function within those rooms. In those rooms, you do these types of tasks only, right? And only certain people can go into a phone booth or can go into the conference room. And then once you are in those rooms, the people who are allowed to go into those rooms, you can sit at tables. Right? And within those tables, there are different types of work that you can do. There is a collaboration table. There is a focus table. There is a whiteboard that's the release lounge. Right? So there is different.
Speaker 1: Functions within those rooms, And the people can move in and out of those rooms and do discrete tasks. And then, As the call, if those discrete tasks and milestones have, you know, one particular agent, they'll get called into that room. And those agents, you know who um you know, might have similar capabilities, but not access, can't go right. So, you've built this framework, And then as you work through phases of your project, maybe it's like the architecture phase. Well, you have your eight, you know, your subject matter expert agent. You have your documentation agent. You have your orchestration agent in a room. And sometimes they're working on their own individual tasks. They're sitting at a desk and they're focused on their monitors. But sometimes they're in the collaboration portion of the room. They're at a big table and they're collaborating on tasks that have multiple dependencies. And sometimes they're at the whiteboard saying, okay, are we ready to launch this? Right? So if you think about it.
Speaker 1: I s this framework of in this building? Only certain accesses to rooms are granted by whatever roles we define, and then each of those rooms has a function and a purpose. And then within those rooms, there are areas for different types of tasks under that function. You build a framework, right? So anyway, that's how I would think about it.
Speaker 2: Okay now, but you haven't mentioned. So so.
Speaker 2: One of the things about these is like that's a lot of like. Okay, that's a lot of getting things set up, but. What about the individual parts of it Right, like you have the individual tasks getting done. Okay, So like each thing that needs to get done, how do those get placed into the queue Like? What is. Does each table have a queue? How does it come in? Where is the input and output of not only the table but the room, like all we not mind like the big part, all way down to like the small. Because, the thing is, is these agents have to be told each tiny little part. The big part, if you tell it the big part, it's going to do all these things, but it's going to miss a lot of little parts. So, you have to basically got to make sure they're going through every single little individual task, because they skip over so much.
Speaker 2: So, if we are like, okay, I have this grand vision of a thing that I want to build, and then it's like, okay, How do I get it to not only just try to like say, oh, it's built after just building like a front end for it that just looks like something, but It would also have to stop. And the user and say, okay, well, if you want to build this, then we're going to have to lay all these other things out because it doesn't really do that right now. It's just kind of like oh okay cool. And he just gets going and get started and just like does stuff. So I need that like back and forth, But without being like how do I say it stupid about it or overbearing because it's like okay, well if there is an obvious answer, like don't ask a question. But it's like okay, if you need to know something to help structure or build this, then it makes sense to ask the questions. Yep. But how do you know when you covered all of the bases?
Speaker 1: Well in a project management, Situation: the first phase is called discovery, right? So, you get all of your functional experts and your stakeholders, whoever they are into a room.
Speaker 2: Before you continue, You mentioned something before we were recording that you mentioned something about going through the project manager, And that's actually one of the reasons I wanted to start recordings because you've mentioned a flow, a path of input. Output, input, output like from from one to the next. Next you you laid that out very so eloquently, and that was something I wanted to get. Yeah, so what you are about to say I think is a part of that.
Speaker 1: Yeah, So typically in like a waterfall format for projects, t here is the discovery phase, The architecture phase slash design phase, right, then t here is the testing phase and the execution phase. So at each, Phase of these things, there is something that's called the go/no-go, right? The sign-off of each of these. And so generally, so to answer the original question, Which is like, how do you get to a place where you feel like you at least have the bare bones of what is needed for that? Well, in project management, What you do is you define the business outcome that you need to know that you've achieved success.
Speaker 1: So that could be, you know, active users, you know, Cases that you are able to solve actual examples of things, whatever it can be. T here is quantifiable outcomes and then from there you back into, You know, defining yourum your start, your end goal and the gap analysis that needs to happen there.
Speaker 2: Okay now. The issue is, and I understand all that. And you know, some things I may not know, some things I may know, but I am still just trying to capture it all anyway. So, But one of the issues that you like are talking about, like adding a feature, for example. Let's say we have building something out and and I know am just i am talking about specifically code, but it doesn't have to be code. This could be actually any other part of business that link that I sent you is like.
Speaker 2: Using Using Claude Code, if you are not a developer, It actually talks about using Claude Code and CoWork together and like how to do that. And. So this is like a good example of that where, so you know, you tell it to build these things. Let's say you want a feature to be able to search through all the records that you have in a database. Like like for example, You need to be able to search quickly through a number of clients. And so you can find whoever you've done business for and pull them up. Mhm. Well, so it'll build that right, So it'll build out an interface and you're expecting a number of things on it, right? So you would expect a search bar. You would expect to see the grid that you can scroll. But what if it did that? But it so all that's there, like you can search. But it um let's say it's missing the.
Speaker 2: The columns that you need, let's say it gives you just the description, so the name column. Or let's say it only shows you the top one hundred. It doesn't actually do what you really like. It doesn't. It's not or or let's say you are like, oh, I wanted to filter for active and inactive. And um, You know, so it builds that in, but only if you let's say type it in, so it's not actually how you want it right. So you can test against that. It can build it and it can test and say," Oh, well, it's in there,", but you won't know until you with your human eyes go and look at it. So, how is that preventable to make sure that it is actually building what you ask it to build? And if it adds interface features, That they actually are wired up;. They're not just sitting there like like It's,
Speaker 1: Like an empty.
Speaker 2: Right, like you have like these things that look like they work but they don't. Like, How do you guarantee that that happens because that's one of the problems I am having is like it says it's done, it tests everything. There is no bugs so it thinks it's fine. It's like, well, yeah, there is no bugs. You didn't put the code in there.
Speaker 1: Yeah so. That is like prompt, and we're starting to get to prompt engineering.
Speaker 2: Kind of kind of.
Speaker 1: So I'll tell you how I deal with it with humans because. Humans have all kinds of interpretations of the exact same words,
Speaker 2: And that's what I need is yeah.
Speaker 1: So for humans, there is a couple things that I do. Um, and actually this is less about project management and more about M and A. So for M and A, A lot of the work that you do is quantifying risk without being able to see what's actually going on in the company. You are acquiring in detail. Right? You can only get indicators. So what I've developed, Is this risk questionnaire and it's a template, and essentially every subject matter expert is responsible for saying, "I am I am giving you my final recommendations based on this. I am putting my name next to it," and it has a list of, um, questions and then it requires you to your subject matter expert to.
Speaker 1: Put their name next to it and say, " like I certify that this is my personal risk assessment based on what I know here." So it's not just like, "Did I look at it?" Yes, it's "I looked at it and," It requires input. So I looked at it and it indicated blank. And they have to fill in the blanks. They can't just say, "I looked at it." They have to say, "I looked." At the high claims statement in their benefits file, And found that there was maybe high claims in the in the frontline hourly workers, or no one has taken any long term disability this year, or not many childbearing female identifying women in this census. Right? Something they have to quantify.
Speaker 1: Something that they've looked at, And that's how I know that they've actually read and considered and thought about the document. They can't just say yes, no, Maybe ;. They have to have independent thought shown in some sort of way during that review process. And so, That is generally how I work through some of this stuff, where not only do you have to. Um, have somebody say," Oh, yeah, I went through it,", but it's critical enough that we need to make sure that they've deeply thought about this before we say, yes/ no/ go. Um, and in for humans that works really well. I don't know what the AI equivalent of that is.
Speaker 2: Well, I mean it's really human design. And so it's up to us to figure out how we want that. So I can, Employ you and say, "You have these tools to do a job, and you know what those tools are and how to use them. If you're skilled, if you're unskilled, then you don't know. You just look at the tool and be like, 'I don't even know how to hold it.'" Yes. And that's the same thing with the AI. So I have to program into the app, what like I have to program it in using programming. Yes, To tell the AI, the things that it needs to know so that it's interpreted properly. So it understands the tool that is being handed.
Speaker 2: Right, So it needs to know the properties to pass along what it needs to fill out. What information goes in, what to expect back out. The input and output of it all is really everything. So like everything has an input and output, right? So you are inputting and outputting your chat. So you input a chat, the AI takes that and it processes it well. It has like these other things like plugins and connectors and you know tools. The tools are the big thing right now MCP servers is a Kind of tool, so it has a tool that the tool takes an input, which is a kind of an output from the AI to the tool. So the the tool has an input, it does its thing, and then it has an output. Sometimes it would go back to the AI, sometimes it'll go to another tool or a different whatever. Yep. And so those are all in code now. When it goes back to the AI, then AI processes that output that it gets that data that is returned.
Speaker 2: To it, And so this is the sort of framework that I need to make sure they all have. That I don't necessarily have built in right now, where it's all sloppy messy, where each one is sort of like its own kind of mishmash thing. And I try to standardize it, but I realize I can't without breaking literally the actual app itself. And then I am essentially redoing it anyway. So why not just start fresh? And then I have one that kind of half works. And i have example code for it to look at that works like. So. What I do want, though, is that agentic framework. So the inputs and outputs are very important, especially when you are trying to figure out how to build agentic teams. Yes, So I want things. So right now like I know, a lot of people are using agents for a lot of different reasons and I am specifically thinking about code. I am specifically thinking about one thing one guy can do at a time. Like you cannot go like you can't just take two developers.
Speaker 2: And put them together and just get things done faster. It doesn't work like that. They can't work on the same code at the same time. Like, things don't, work like that in development. Correct. And so like I can't just have two agents building, code because they're going to overwrite each other's stuff. They're not going to know what function they want to act like. What's the name of this thing that it built? Does it even exist? There is no knowledge of what's there. There, so that's why I typically keep things one at a time. But I know, like with other things, There are like you can have a team of agents that write individually a chapter of a book. Yes, right? Yes, So you can have like a, you know, like a technical book, for example, where they don't even have to know about what the other one's writing, because it's all standard knowledge. Like it's not standard knowledge, but it's knowledge that they have that they know right? It's it's like scientific information. It's always going to be the same.
Speaker 2: No matter what, so you can write chapter after chapter. You can write, chapter nine and then go back and write chapter two of a scientific book. Yes, but when it comes to like flow, um when it comes to like artistic stuff or anything creative that usually changes. You know because it's always kind of like one thing matters, like t here is dependencies, like how one it's it's. It's the butterfly effect. How one thing happened is going to affect the rest of it forever, and we don't know how big or small, right? So, you can't just jump in and do the end and then go back to the beginning unless you are definitively sure that that's what you want the end to be, and then you need to figure out the middle. And maybe that's also a way. Maybe that is also something else I can tell. I can use AI for maybe there are benefits to thinking that way and having specific understandings of.
Speaker 2: Like knowing, like okay, things aren't working for us this way because it's not scientific. Maybe we need to get creative. Maybe we need to we want this end result, We have this beginning. Now let's figure out the meat in the middle that gets us there.
Speaker 1: That's, that's the best way to do it because it requires theum AI to explain to you how it's thinking before it actually starts executing right?
Speaker 2: That's actually smart yeah. Well, cause that's what planning mode is basically supposed to be.
Speaker 1: Right, well that's exactly it. So it's just like a human, right? You say this is where we are today. We're going to define exactly the restraints and constrictions that are there, right? All the inputs here is where we are going. These are the necessary outputs. And here are the necessary, you know, formats, all the things right now. How would you approach that and you ask your planner? And then. You stop and you ask your subject matter experts, and then you stop and you ask your technological agents. Right, you basically build these agents, and you put them in a room. Right, you build these agents with their specific functional expertise. You put them in a planning room. Right, iterate. You get everybody's opinion, then you consolidate those things into milestones, discrete tasks signoffs.
Speaker 1: Tests scenarios, right? All the things that you run, and then at each stage you reassess: did this work? Did, you know, did we hit all the milestones or have we covered what we plan to get to? It's just like a project management um, you know executive committee. Right? You review, as you go through each stage of the process, : did we do what we set out to do in the framework of.
Speaker 1: Discovery. One Of the fun things, One of the funny things that this will do is so I'll tell it after it writes something, I'll say," I found different terminology." I'll say," You know, okay, write a test. Write tests for the code." You know, so we have unit testing; we have feature testing; all that. Um and it's funny though, because I've seen it like in its thinking,; it'll go through and be like, oh, this is failing.
Speaker 2: This is failing. Okay, well, let's just change the test so it passes. It's like, no, you don't change the test. Right? Like the whole point of testing it is to make sure that it.
Speaker 1: And, that's why you build a room. That's the testing room. And the framework is always do not change the test scenarios report accurately right Well, right. Right.
Speaker 2: Um. And and that's actually what I did is like I have it written in there to where like the test agent isn't allowed to just make the test work. It. S upposed to report back failures, so that way the failures can get picked up and then the failures are fixed.
Speaker 1: Right, and what I am challenging you to do, and I think you are hearing this is that like don't change the agent, change the framework.
Speaker 2: Exactly right. So basically, change how they're allowed to behave when they enter that.
Speaker 1: Whatever segment.
Speaker 2: Yeah, I am going to have to find a good way to say it because it makes sense to use human terms. Like regular people terminology, so like sitting down at a table makes sense. Sitting at a table in a room because we have a chat room. That's how a lot of the backend code works. It calls it a room in the sockets. Um, to-dos is something that the AI understands very easily what that means, So it helps it to just tell it to do a to-do or create a list of to-do s. And it'll do that with.
Speaker 2: Without with very little effort, it's where if I tell it to do a task, it's like well this could be a very long. It's like um behaves differently. So I've noticed that too. And then like milestones are thing it does what I want but, it wants to check off milestones and too ambitiously, so. I I do need it to be more thoughtful, and that's why okay. And that's also why, I am trying to keep it in a very small scope each agent. Like call out is supposed to be a very small scope of work, But what I am also trying to do is limit the context that they need to do the job. I don't want to have to pass like because each agent that runs it runs in its own space in its own context window. Like, it doesn't have, it doesn't share the main chat context.;, it doesn't have all of what I've chatted about.
Speaker 1: It only gets what it was just told to do that one time. Yes. Could, you have essentially like a PA system where the orchestrator just calls people to rooms and the room provides the context?
Speaker 2: So, that's basically what the tasking system does is it assigns agents specific agents to the task that needs to get done. And then so they're supposed to basically go into a meeting together. That's how it works right now anyway. They go into a meeting together. And then that's when they're supposed to like chat with each other about it and then figure out how they're going to do it and what they do next. And that's where, like, I started breaking stuff. And then that's when I realized I needed to, like, everything's been like okay i need I need to do more. I need to do more. So it's like I need to build more things out.
Speaker 1: Yeah, You need to build more architecture so that you can like vary. So that way, when you are like nitpicking things that you need to change, you are only just changing discrete things right?
Speaker 2: And the problem that I am having is I can't get to an MVP baseline where everything works just fine. And then I can just add one thing. Yeah. Right, I want the i'm I'm like in order for this, i I keep finding prerequisites and and um dependencies that it's like I keep getting stuck in the middle of dependencies and prerequisites. And it's like so, I'm like building and then using building and then go. It's like, I'm in this like swimming back and forth, where I need to get to a baseline. And then everything works fine. And it's like okay, Add this one feature test, right, make sure everything works. Yeah everything's done. Okay now.
Speaker 2: Next, test it. And instead of doing like okay, let's add this, add this, add this. And it's like and so many things are going on at once. But it's like I almost have to do it that way first to know what I can do, how like I have. But that's yeah It's like it's like I have to do that. I have to take three steps forward, so i I can take two steps back. Yeah. Because that'll make everything better.
Speaker 1: You are in a conceptualization phase where you are trying to understand what you actually need for to be considered successful. One thing I'll encourage you to do that I think would be very smart is to share all these analogies with your your, you know, Agents or whatever your main chat and see what the feedback is from your AI. Like, what's going on?
Speaker 2: That's why I am recording it too. The transcription of this.
Speaker 1: Yeah, So like what is the you know analogy of the building and the room and you know the desk and the and the conference table and the whiteboard? Like what what is the best way to build that within your framework, right?
Speaker 2: Well, Right, because it's not necessarily like I I'm going to probably use it mostly for code, but maybe I won't. You know but let's say I have it out there, it's open source for other people to pick up. What would they want to use it for? You know maybe you know like, Like that, like that link I sent you. It's likeum, an attorney won, um, Anthropic's hackathon hackathon. Yeah, and I thought that was pretty cool to like see. I don't know if that's true or not. I didn't really like look into it. I would imagine it is, but like, I do understand, which it's a little hard for me to understand that knowing what I know about like attorneys in their what they can and can't do. But anyway,
Speaker 1: Hey don't let Lucy hear you say that she can do all kinds of.
Speaker 2: Yeah, it's just if you are going to be so public about something, I wonder like yeah because it's really hard for judges to accept anything that's done with AI. So I wonder like exactly what maybe like how they did it, because if it's just code, because staff can use AI fine, but there are a lot of legal things that like.
Speaker 1: Maybe that's just someone who's got a hobby project like you at home.
Speaker 2: It's possible. I am curious about those one mean.
Speaker 1: So, why I say that this like framework is so important, I think you and I are thinking about it in the same way. It's like okay, so you have your engineer agents, you have your Scrum agent, you have your whatever right? Like you are running Agile functionality right? You've got your baseline set up. Yeah. Okay, well, now you want to run a project that has coding elements, but you know is an overall project. It's got other elements as well. Okay, build a new room. You build a new function. You set the security around who can go in and out of that room. You set the function of that room to be about writing, project governance, documents or whatever, right? But you've built the framework there where it's like okay, So you are just actually adding a room to the system that already exists. And you are adding new subject matter experts with different expertise, and you are updating that room's security so that, you know.
Speaker 1: Some of your existing agents can go in, but also your new agents can go in, right? So if you've built this framework, you can iterate on that for different functions because you Discord.
Speaker 2: So what you are describing can easily be easily be done with like a Discord style layout because you go into Discord, and that's what you do. You create these rooms, you create these different chatum like like, you haveum. Groups and the way that they break out the permissions, it can be very granular, it can be very global. And, so you have some rooms where you go in, and you can't just chat. ;, you can ask a question and post it, And then it becomes like a sub- chat of that room, where people can only chat about that thing. And once it's answered, then it's done and closed. Yep which is your.
Speaker 2: Exactly, which basically what you are saying. Like when you sit at a table, that would be your behavior. Like you can only do certain things certain ways, and that's one of the examples of what that looks like. Yeah, so you have to basically go. You can't just chat and then anybody chat back to no. You ask a question, and then somebody basically says, oh, I am going to go help them. And they pick it up. And then so you go in together into a sub chat of that room. So maybe it'd be like sitting down at a table and then finding somebody to help you and then sitting next to them, and then just working with them yeah at your table.
Speaker 1: And then, In your table analogy, sorry if I may, in your table analogy, What happens is you have given them a format for collaborating the discrete tasks that they're collaborating on. And then also a template for output. So at the end, You are the sign off right of tasks that reach level, whatever level, three risk or something. And so then they give you in format ninety seven percent pass rate. Um, you know, here are the things. Here is where you can find our read me. Here is where you can find the blah. And here are all the elements for you to sign off on the execution of this task, right? And some tasks rise to the level of you need discrete, you know, you need actual push a button sign off on these things. And. Some of them are as long as the documentation lives somewhere, and I can reference it in a template, go ahead and execute right. Move to the whiteboard and execute with with whomever. The orchestrator is.
Speaker 1: Um, so yes, Like the idea of closing things out is what that's how I would think about it for your app. Is high level stuff has to have some, you know, some output template that gets an approver to say, yes, execute. And some are lower than that. And as long as documentation lives somewhere in your data, then go ahead and execute.
Speaker 2: Yeah, so you have, You can sit down at a table. You can work with one person, and so that's like the one person. So, you are like chatting with them back and forth on whatever you are working on, or you can basically turn and chat with the whole table, right? So that's like exactly like Discord. Yep, Where you have anybody who decides to go to that table and sit down has joined the chat room. Well. In this case, It's not going to be because I just chose to go there ;. It's because well, we're all assigned to work on the same together, so it would make sense. And, then you can take whatever you are working on and package it up in one way or another. Some chats do like you can type commands and get like a report. ; you can get like AI to summarize things. ; you can do all kinds of stuff there.
Speaker 2: Midjourney is an AI image generation that was one of the first image generations that was really popular. Well, it was it's only in Discord, so if you want to use Midjourney, You have to go into Discord and go into a chat room, and you use a slash command. And then like you know, request an image get made with your prompt. And it's there for anybody in there to see your image come through, You know, or you can go into like a direct message chat with the AI and get one. You know, So that's where you like pay like a little more of a premium or whatever. So they have these different reasons that you would do different things. Of course, that's more of like a sales model, But it still provides the example of that. We would have these different capabilities if you use that if use that analogy as a framework. I like the I think the Discord analogy or i I just use Discord because that's what I am most familiar with, but.
Speaker 2: What that also does is it lets you tag other things. You can tag another channel, so that would basically or in this case, you can tag another table. So it instantly becomes like a reference to whatever's going on. You could even in Discord link directly to a very specific line in the chat, like somebody's actual submission. And I think something like that would be really helpful in like an AI scenario where you can, um, cite a specific thing that was said or chatted about.
Speaker 1: Yep, right. Like go back into the record.
Speaker 2: But yeah, But the AI can actually use that to tell each other stuff and reference things without having to rewrite it. So it's like a sort of a cache becauseum.
Speaker 2: One of the other things that I did learn is that. So like Minimax has the capability to use caching, So you are not using much like even though I don't use a lot of tokens anyway, Now I use even less tokens because it has a prompt like a yeah like caching capabilities where it's not like, like if if certain things are similar enough. I don't know exactly how it works. I can read about it to find out but I haven't yet. But basically, the gist of it is if it's Similar enough, It'll cache it to where it doesn't have to pull all the information or send all the information a bunch of times. Yeah, which is this you know what caching is. So, um, So high cache hits are typically a lot cheaper than well. They are always a lot cheaper than like a full blown call. Right makes sense. Um and so like leveraging things like that can make a lot of these.
Speaker 2: Like the caching would actually be more valuable. Yeah, absolutely. Huh, all right. You want to say the same thing to a bunch of bunch of agents, or if you like, yeah.
Speaker 1: Right, you just need to reference something across a lot of different discrete conversations.
Speaker 2: One of the technical challenges that I have is when I am in a chat with an AI agent, the API backend, the model of it you tell it.
Speaker 2: How do I say this. The data that comes through is structured in let's say like JSON format, And in JSON format, you have like a key and pair or a key value sort of structure. It's more complex than that, But that's the basic thing when I say it goes through when I type a chat and it says user. Or or um like like name user.
Speaker 2: And then it'll say, you know, "prompt," and it'll have my prompt. And then when it responds, it'll respond with name assistant and then prompt and then whatever is set back. So, it's basically like it only knows about one other chatterer. Right? And so if I add a third agent into the room. It doesn't necessarily know that there is a third agent in there. It just knows that something was said by that name, by that person, or by that thing, whatever it is. And. So it doesn't really fully understand that it can chat with me or the other agent.
Speaker 1: Right? Yeah, you said that this was an issue. Is it an issue though with just how you've set up the system?
Speaker 2: And again, it gets back to the fundamentals of how it's set up. Where now I need to reword some of this, I need to rename some of it, but I also need it to translate things. So even though I am not using "user" and "agent," that is what the AI backend uses. So I need to get the app itself to be smart enough to know how to manage that and make sure that the AI is fully aware at all times of its place in this. Con versation,
Speaker 1: Right? Yep, that's why I think this framework will be really helpful. Is because then it doesn't have to keep track of so many things. It when it's in You know the, the discovery room. There's a template that it runs through. With all of the agents that are there, with the sole purpose of you know a specific output. That's what that room always does. Right. Um.
Speaker 1: Anyway, yes, I hear what you are saying. I think you are on to something really good.
Speaker 2: Yeah, cause yeah right like you don't go to a laundry room to make dinner.
Speaker 1: Right well and and I think that that's kind of what I am thinking about is.
Speaker 2: Like you have certain tools in the laundry room that you don't have in the kitchen.
Speaker 1: Right exactly You go into a conference room to do conferences. You go into, you know a cubicle to focus on your own work. You go to a, You know, a collaboration room to brainstorm. You know, they all of these room types have their own purpose. And when you define what that purpose is, and you only allow certain functions and agent types to go into those rooms, right? Then all of a sudden, you don't actually really need to worry about. Okay, they forgot all this stuff because the parameters are built in there. You can always.
Speaker 1: You know, update the parameters or make a new room or whatever, right? But essentially you have these structures that are scalable. It just it reminds me of like enterprise enterprise systems, right? The back end of enterprise systems. You have like security. You have definitions of user types. You have definitions of access within those user types and domains. And then you have the output functions, right? Mhm. So you are just building your version of that.
Speaker 2: Yes, and there is so many different ways to do it, and I am trying to build a way that makes sense, that works, And it offers like it's a good way to program it, but it's also a good way to use it. Yeah,
Speaker 1: And it's intuitive enough that like. You can. It's not hard to understand how you would leverage whatever system that you're going to create, whatever framework. I think you have some really good ideas. I'm curious what when you give it this transcript, What your your AI is going to tell you is the translation of this into its understanding of its own functionality. So when you do that, let me know because that'll be really interesting.
Speaker 2: Yeah, I mean, I'll use this chat and then I have some other things. What are you doing?
Speaker 1: There's a fucking moth. Which means that there's something in my fucking laundry. Okay. Washing hands. That means it's.