Speaker 1: I Love You. I really like talking to you about this stuff. I know I don't have like much of a practical helpful, but I like talking to you about it.
Matt Rogers: Yeah, I mean, I am gonna, obviously feed it more information and ideas and things that I've been thinking and the stuff that I know. I've been doing and you know, I don't want it to redo some certain things, so I probably won't mention some things. Um, you know, I am gonna build it out or i am gonna. I have some ideas in my head, but.
Matt Rogers: One of the hard parts is that like I want, to have a lot of information in front of me. Um, And it does a really good job of trying to cram a bunch of things into all these panels. All on one screen, but it's like. I really need to have all the information in a more consumable manner. Like I need to be able to look at. A part of it at a time. And um.
Matt Rogers: I think that's, you know, bite size. Build it like we were saying earlier. Build it out in bite sized pieces. Don't do all this grand stuff all at once. So it's like when I so I am gonna have to restart. I am gonna have to build out like the back end when I build out piece by piece. Um, I have to start. So basically, I have to scaffold it out with the base design, because it seems like once that's in place, it does not change it so like once it gets the like, The UI kind of like figured out, it is like pulling teeth to get it to really like change. The layout or anything, so if I don't like it, I like that's where you reiterate, you restart, restart, restart until you get. What, do you want the way it looks? And then you go from there and then you build on it. And so that's kind of where I am at now. But I've just done that more on like more than just the UI. I've done on the app level. Yeah. But yeah so like.
Matt Rogers: Once I get it to start to kind of like, okay, I like how it looks. Let's add to this and then you know. Basically figure out how so that's where like I think one of the big things if I can find like a UI. Cause there is a lot of like Canva has a lot of UI like interface templates. There is a lot of templating out there to find. There is a lot of examples. It's like oh, so if I can tell it, if I can give it an example, especially if it has like HTML code or anything. If I can find an interface like template example, feed it that, and then that would be a great starting point. And then start building on these like agentic features and the coding features. But I do want it to be very powerful without being like heavy. There is a lot of really good ways to write code and write build out apps where things don't have these like.
Matt Rogers: Um. Ooh. How, do you say it like you don't have theseum I want to say magical, but like just these. These parts of it that like, Why does it behave You know? You don't understand why the behavior is doing what it's doing because it just doesn't make sense. If you build it out right, you won't even have to worry about that.
Speaker 1: Yep, great.
Speaker 1: Because it has its own checks and balances that you've iterated.
Matt Rogers: Standardized, right? The standardized stuff. And yeah, like I was saying, that inputs and outputs, you know, like oversimplifying. But yeah, If I can just have like a standardized input and an output for modules, then. Yep. You know like. Yep. Like as a concept, and that would be okay. Well, every module always has to supply the app with this. Yep You know it's like or you know it's like basically like have these options, right? It's like an AI or AI. It's like an API basically.
Speaker 1: Yeah, well, I think of it like think of it as like a RFP, right? Like at the beginning t here is all these questions that every single vendor needs to answer. Do you have the capabilities You know, all this stuff, Right Like. And then the output is not only the answers, but then also the gap analysis. And you know where you want to go from there. Anyway, go ahead. Yeah when i am building when.
Matt Rogers: I am building a module. I just realized it is. I am basically having it talk to the app in an API sort of way. It's just not using an API. It's just using a back channel that I created using sockets.